OKAY, CHANDLER.
OKAY.
AND YOUR HOROSCOPE SAYS
"ON THE FIFTH, A SPECIAL SOMEONE
IS GOING TO GIVE YOU A GIFT."
OH, WELL, THANK
YOU IN ADVANCE.
OH, BUT THE 12th
BRINGS A LOVERS' SPAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE A JOKE
ABOUT MY SPECIAL PRESENT.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
OH, WAIT, AND ON THE 19th
"A SECRET CRUSH
ANNOUNCES ITSELF."
HEY, GUYS.
HEY!
OH, MY GOD,
IT'S JOEY TRIBBIANI
OF MAC AND C.H.E.E.S.E.!
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S YOUR FIRST DAY.
SO, ARE YOU PSYCHED
TO FIGHT FAKE CRIME
WITH YOUR ROBOT SIDEKICK?
AM I PSYCHED?
THE LEAD IN MY OWN TV SERIES?
I'VE DREAMED ABOUT THIS
FOR YEARS!
WHY HAVE I NOT BEEN PREPARING?
NO, JOEY,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE GREAT.
BUT I GOT TO ACT
WITH A ROBOT, PHEEBS
AND I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT TECHNOLOGY.
I CAN'T EVEN USE CHANDLER'S
COMPUTER, EXCEPT TO FIND PORN.
AND THAT'S ONLY
'CAUSE IT'S RIGHT THERE
WHEN YOU TURN IT ON.
I THINK OUR LOVERS' SPAT
WILL START A LITTLE EARLY
THIS MONTH.
I'LL BE WAITING.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GOING TO BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
ARE YOU JUDGING THEM
BY THEIR COVERS?
'CAUSE YOU'RE REALLY
NOT SUPPOSED TO DO THAT.
NO, I'M JUST DECIDING
WHICH ONE TO USE.
I'M GOING TO START
WRITING ANOTHER BOOK.
B-BECAUSE THE LAST ONE
WAS SUCH A BIG SELLER?
WELL, IF YOU MUST KNOW,
I HAVE WRITTEN 14 BOOKS
AND, AS I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAS READ THEM
I CAN TELL YOU THAT THEY HAVE
ALL BEEN VERY WELL-RECEIVED.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING LATER?
OH, RACHEL AND I
HAVE APPOINTMENTS
TO GET OUR HAIR CUT.
WE DO?
I WANT TO SEE WHAT HE WANTS.
OH.
I JUST FOUND OUT ELIZABETH'S DAD
WANTS TO MEET ME.
WAIT A MINUTE;
HOLD THE PHONE--
YOU'RE NOT
ELIZABETH'S DAD?
LOOK, COME ON, GUYS.
I REALLY WANT THIS GUY
TO LIKE ME.
IT WOULD REALLY HELP ME OUT
IF YOU GUYS COULD BE HERE
TO KIND OF MAKE ME LOOK GOOD.
WE CAN BE HERE.
OH, OF COURSE!
THANKS.
WE KNOW HOW TOUGH
THOSE PARENT-TEACHER
CONFERENCES CAN BE.
SO, HERE'S
YOUR OFFICE SET.
WOW, HUH?
MAC MACAVELLI,
PRIVATE INVESTIGATOR.
HUH?
LET'S, UH, GET YOU TO WARDROBE
FOR A FITTING.
OKAY-- HEY, UH, WHEN DO
I GET TO MEET THE ROBOT?
WHY DON'T WE DO THAT
RIGHT NOW?
HE'S RIGHT HERE.
OKAY.
JOEY TRIBBIANI,
THIS IS...
OH, MY... WOW!
HE'S SO LIFELIKE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS IS WAYNE.
THE MAN WHO CREATED
AND OPERATES C.H.E.E.S.E.
HOW DO YOU DO,
THERE, WAYNE?
I'LL LET YOU TWO GUYS
GET ACQUAINTED, HUH?
OKAY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
UH, SO, WHERE'S
C.H.E.E.S.E.?
C.H.E.E.S.E.
IS RIGHT HERE.
( electronic voice ):
NICE TO MEET YOU, MAC.
( laughing )
THIS IS, LIKE,
THE TEMPORARY
ROBOT, RIGHT?
NO. WHY?
WELL, I JUST THOUGHT
IT WAS GOING TO BE
LIKE, A REALLY COOL ROBOT,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE THE TERMINATOR
OR, UH, WHEN I
FIRST SAW YOU.
I SPENT TWO YEARS
DEVELOPING THIS MACHINE.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY
STATE-OF-THE-ART.
I'M SORRY, IT JUST...
IT DOESN'T REALLY LOOK LIKE
IT CAN DO ANYTHING.
IT CAN DO THIS.
WHOO!
THIS IS MY FATHER,
PAUL STEVENS.
DAD, THIS IS
ROSS GELLER.
IT-IT-IT'S GREAT
TO MEET YOU, PAUL.
I USUALLY PREFER
LIZ'S BOYFRIENDS
TO ADDRESS ME
AS MR. STEVENS.
WELL, OF COURSE,
OF COURSE, MR. STEVENS.
SO, ROSS...
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
EXCUSE ME?
WHY CAN'T YOU GET A
GIRLFRIEND YOU OWN AGE?
OH, IT'S FUNNY.
UM...
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I DON'T LIKE YOU
GOING OUT WITH
MY DAUGHTER, ROSS.
OKAY, UM... I CAN,
I CAN SEE THAT.
UM, BUT I THINK
IF YOU GIVE ME,
UM, ONE CHANCE
I-I CAN CHANGE
YOUR MIND.
OKAY.
WHAT?
OKAY, I'LL GIVE YOU ONE CHANCE
TO CHANGE MY MIND.
YOU GOT ONE MINUTE.
DADDY...
FINE.
TWO MINUTES.
GO.
( sputtering )
( chuckling )
A MINUTE, 50 SECONDS.
OKAY, UM...
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I HAVE NEVER
DONE ANYTHING
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN IN, UM,
RELATIONSHIPS IN GENERAL,
BUT I'VE NEVER DONE
IT WITH A STUDENT.
I MEAN, I... NOT...
NOT "IT"... I MEAN...
I DON'T MEAN...
WE HAVEN'T DONE "IT."
UH, WE... I MEAN,
WE'VE DONE STUFF,
BUT I...
OKAY, OKAY.
A JOKE, A JOKE.
LIGHTEN THE MOOD.
UM, TWO GUYS
GO INTO A BAR.
ONE OF THEM'S IRISH...
I'M IRISH.
AND THE IRISH GUY
WINS THE JOKE.
ROSS!
HOW CRAZY THAT WE
WOULD RUN INTO YOU.
OH, MY GOD, THANK YOU.
UM, UH, MR. STEVENS,
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET MY FRIENDS.
THIS IS PHOEBE, MONICA
AND CHANDLER.
SO YOU'RE
ELIZABETH'S FATHER, HUH?
I CAN SEE NOW
WHERE SHE GETS HER...
RUGGED HANDSOMENESS.
IS THERE A MRS. STEVENS?
THERE'S A MR. BING.
NO.
UNFORTUNATELY,
LIZZY'S MOM PASSED AWAY
SHORTLY AFTER SHE WAS BORN.
I RAISED HER BY MYSELF.
OH!
I GET THAT A LOT.
OKAY.
UM, WHY DON'T WE ALL
TAKE A SEAT, YOU KNOW?
AND, UH, AND I'LL GET
US ALL SOME COFFEES.
YEAH, WHY DON'T YOU...?
( clears throat )
UH, AND YOU GUYS CAN
TALK ABOUT WHATEVER...
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER
POPS INTO YOUR HEAD.
IT IS SO STRANGE
SEEING ROSS HERE
AT THIS TIME OF DAY
'CAUSE USUALLY, WELL,
HE'S AT THE CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL.
YEAH.
NOT LOOKING
FOR DATES.
SO, UH, MONICA
IS ROSS'S SISTER.
YEAH. HE'S A GREAT BROTHER.
I HAD A SISTER.
OH.
SHE PASSED AWAY.
OH!
OH, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DO THAT EVERY TIME.
BUT, UH, ROSS, ROSS
IS A GREAT GUY.
I, UH, WAS ROOMMATES
WITH HIM IN COLLEGE.
FUNNY STORY--
YOUR ROOMMATE IN COLLEGE
DIED, DIDN'T HE?
A PART OF HIM DID, YES.
OKAY, HERE WE ARE--
PAUL, ELIZABETH.
SO, I HOPE YOU GUYS
WERE FINDING SOMETHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
YES. WE WERE JUST...
HI, SORRY I'M LATE,
BUT I AM READY.
READY TO TALK YOU UP.
WHEN DOES LIZ'S FATHER
GET HERE?
I'M ALREADY HERE.
OH!
ROSS IS SO GREAT.
HEY, HONEY, YOU GOT THE KIND
WITH THE LITTLE GIRL.
YOU SAID WE'D GET THE KIND
WITH THE BABY.
NO, YOU SAID THE BABY
CREEPS YOU OUT.
NO, THE LITTLE GIRL
CREEPS ME OUT.
YOU SAID THE BABY.
WHY WOULD THE BABY
CREEP ME OUT?
WHY WOULD THE LITTLE GIRL
CREEP YOU OUT?
GUYS, I'M SORRY, CAN YOU PLEASE
TALK A LITTLE SLOWER?
THIS IS GOING
IN YOUR BOOK?
YEAH. IT'S ABOUT RELATIONSHIPS.
YOU KNOW, THE TRAPS,
THE PITFALLS, WHAT NOT TO DO.
KEEP GOING.
THIS STUFF'S GREAT.
WHAT?!
EXCUSE ME...
AND HOW NONE OF IT MATTERS
WHEN THE PEOPLE
REALLY LOVE EACH OTHER.
AND HOW PEOPLE WILL BELIEVE
ANYTHING YOU TELL THEM
AS LONG AS IT'S A COMPLIMENT.
OH, HI.
HI.
I THINK I LEFT MY KEYS
HERE SOMEWHERE.
OH, WELL, LET'S LOOK FOR THEM.
USUALLY UNDER
HERE, THEY'RE...
OH, OH, HEY, HEY,
ARE THESE THEM?
NO.
ALL RIGHT.
OH!
HERE THEY ARE
RIGHT HERE.
OH, GOOD.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
YEAH-- WAIT!
OH, SORRY, MR. PAUL,
MR. PAUL.
JUST CALL ME PAUL.
PAUL.
UM, I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT, YOU KNOW,
ROSS REALLY IS A GREAT GUY.
WELL, MAYBE YOU
COULD DATE HIM, THEN.
THAT WOULD SAVE ME THE
TROUBLE OF KILLING HIM.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU JUST DON'T LOOK OLD ENOUGH
TO HAVE A 20-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER.
WELL, WE WERE VERY
YOUNG WHEN WE HAD HER.
OH, WE?
WELL, YEAH.
IT USUALLY TAKES
TWO PEOPLE TO...
OH, NO! YES!
OF COURSE...
I KNOW THAT.
I MEANT, ARE YOU STILL "WE,"
OR ARE YOU JUST "YOU"?
I'M JUST ME, YEAH.
MY WIFE DIED SHORTLY
AFTER LIZZY WAS BORN.
OH!
SO YOU RAISED HER
ALL ON YOUR OWN?
YES, I DID.
OH! OH...
All:
HEY.
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY?
PRETTY GREAT.
I DID GET A LITTLE ATTITUDE
FROM THE ROBOT.
DAMN THOSE ROBOTS.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
OUR FAITHFUL SERVANTS!
ANYWAY, IT WASN'T THE ROBOT,
IT WAS THE GUY WHO CONTROLS HIM.
YEAH, HE DOESN'T LIKE ME.
HE HAD C.H.E.E.S.E. KNOCK OVER
THE SANDWICH TABLE
RIGHT WHEN I WAS REACHING
FOR ONE-- OH!
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GET HIM FIRED?
I MAY HAVE TO.
I HATE TO DO IT,
BUT I'M THE STAR, YOU KNOW?
THERE'S A LIMIT
TO HOW MANY SANDWICHES
I CAN EAT OFF THE FLOOR.
( cell phone rings )
EXCUSE ME.
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
JOE! I'M GLAD I FOUND YOU!
I GOT AN AUDITION FOR YOU!
Wow!
The thing is,
it's kind of on the Q.T.
THE ACTOR WHO HAS THE PART
DOESN'T KNOW HE MIGHT BE FIRED.
It's a lead in a series--
MAC AND C.H.E.E.S.E.
I'M THE LEAD IN
MAC AND C.H.E.E.S.E.!
UH-OH!
JOEY?
HI, ROSS.
I WAS JUST GETTING HIM
TO LIKE YOU.
JOEY!
JOEY?!
HEY, ROSS.
ROSS, JOEY IS NOT HERE.
OKAY, I'LL JUST
WAIT FOR HIM IN HERE.
ROSS, IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN COME OUT.
YEAH, ROSS, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ME, MR. STEVENS.
PAUL, I DIDN'T...
OH, MY GOSH,
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE YOU.
SURE YOU DID.
YOU CAME IN,
YOU GOT ALL AWKWARD.
YOU RAN TO THE BEDROOM.
YOU WERE SHOUTING
"JOEY! JOEY!"
BYE, RACHEL.
BYE.
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
OKAY. SEE YOU.
BYE, ROSS.
WHAT...
WHAT... HOW...
WHAT THE... HOW... WHAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW, HE LOST HIS KEYS
SO HE WAS LOOKING FOR THEM.
IN YOUR MOUTH?
NO...
DOWNSTAIRS,
AND WE GOT TO TALKING,
YOU KNOW, FOR, LIKE, TWO HOURS
AND I REALLY LIKED HIM.
SO I INVITED HIM UP HERE
FOR A CUP OF COFFEE.
YOU WERE AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
ROSS, WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
SO I KISSED THE GUY.
HE'S MY GIRLFRIEND'S FATHER,
OKAY?
IT'S... IT'S WEIRD.
YOU DATED MY SISTER.
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
WHAT? WHY?
THIS IS WEIRD FOR ME.
ROSS, LOOK, LOOK...
THIS IS GOOD
FOR YOU, OKAY?
LET'S FACE IT.
SO FAR,
THE GUY'S NOT LOVING YOU
BUT I CAN TURN THAT AROUND.
I GOT THE INSIDE TRACK.
WE CAN ALL GO OUT TO DINNER.
YOU KNOW, AND I
CAN TALK YOU UP.
PLUS, THE GUY IS A VERY,
VERY SUCCESSFUL LAWYER.
HOW IS THAT IMPORTANT?
OH, IT'S IMPORTANT.
SO, APPARENTLY, THERE'S, LIKE,
A MILLION GUYS OUT THERE
THAT CAN PLAY MAC.
AND THERE'S ONLY
THIS ONE ROBOT
AND THIS ONE GUY
WHO CONTROLS IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW
HE COULD GET ME FIRED.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WELL, YOU KNOW, JOEY
YOU'RE A PRETTY
CHARMING GUY.
THANKS, BUT I KIND OF HAVE
A PROBLEM TO DEAL WITH HERE.
NO, SWEETIE,
YOU'VE GOT TO
WIN OVER THE GUY
WHO CONTROLS C.H.E.E.S.E.
YOU GOT TO GO BACK THERE
AND KISS SOME
SERIOUS ROBOT ASS.
THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
OKAY, BUT IF I GOT TO TURN ON
THE CHARM TOMORROW
I'M NOT WASTING ANY MORE OF IT
OVER HERE WITH YOU GUYS.
WELL, ACTUALLY, I GOT A LITTLE
BIT SAVED FOR YOU, PHEEBS.
SO YOU DO YOU THINK, UH,
JOEY'S MORE CHARMING THAN ME?
YEAH. THAT'S WHY I'M SLEEPING
WITH HIM ON THE SIDE.
YEAH, YOU WISH.
"YOU WISH."
PHOEBE, STOP
WRITING ABOUT US.
I'M NOT WRITING ABOUT YOU.
I'M WRITING ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
WHO?
MARSHA AND CHESTER.
OKAY, FINE, FINE.
THEN YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WILL JUST WRITE
ABOUT PHYLLIS.
"PHYLLIS IS SITTING
IN A CHAIR."
OOH.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
"PHYLLIS SEES WHAT I'M DOING."
OOH-HOO.
OOH, I HAVE TASTED MY OWN
MEDICINE AND IT IS BITTER.
MORNING. HEY...
HOW'S MY FAVORITE GENIUS
AND HIS LITTLE ROBOT BUDDY?
DON'T TOUCH HIM.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
UH, ALL RIGHT,
WAYNE... LOOK
LEVEL WITH ME, OKAY?
I KEEP HEARING
ALL THESE RUMORS
THAT I MIGHT GET FIRED.
THEY EVEN HAVE
ACTORS COMING IN
TO READ FOR MY PART.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU GOT TO GIVE ME
A SECOND CHANCE.
I MEAN, I LOVE
THIS LITTLE GUY...
OKAY.
THAT'S WHY YOU
DIDN'T WANT ME TO
TOUCH HIM, RIGHT?
HERE YOU GO.
STUPID...
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
GOD...
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
SO, IT SEEMED
THAT MY PROM DATE
HAD STOOD ME UP,
SO ROSS SELFLESSLY
OFFERED TO TAKE ME.
WHAT A NICE STORY.
SO ROSS WAS IN COLLEGE
AND DECIDED TO JUMP
AT THE CHANCE
TO TAKE A YOUNG GIRL
TO HER HIGH SCHOOL PROM.
WOW...
I DEFINITELY DID NOT SEE
THAT ONE BACKFIRING.
I'M GOING TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
YEAH, TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU KNOW, JUST SO YOU KNOW
I WAS A FRESHMAN
AND SHE WAS A SENIOR.
SO IT WASN'T AS BAD AS...
ROSS, LOOK, I KNOW I
HAVE BEEN GIVING YOU
A LOT OF JABS
AND IT'S PARTLY
BECAUSE I'M VERY
PROTECTIVE OF LIZZY
AND PARTLY BECAUSE, WELL,
THEY JUST KEEP COMING TO ME.
BUT I HAVE TO
ADMIT THAT AFTER
ALL THE WONDERFUL THINGS
LIZZY HAS TOLD ME
AND THE MANY, MANY,
MANY STORIES
THAT RACHEL
HAS TOLD ME
THAT, WELL...
YOU'RE NOT... ALL BAD.
"NOT ALL BAD."
AND YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY
I WAS SO HARSH BEFORE
BUT YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
I STILL LOOK AT LIZZY
LIKE SHE'S A
12-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
I DO THAT, TOO.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
NO, NO, I'M NOT...
I DON'T MEAN I SEE HER
AS A 12-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
I MEAN,
I HAVE A SON WHO'S SIX
AND I STILL THINK OF HIM
AS A BABY.
YOU HAVE A SON?
WELL, MY EX-WIFE AND I
SHARE CUSTODY OF BEN
AND, UH, JUST
SO YOU KNOW
CAROL AND I ARE
ON EXCELLENT TERMS
AS I'M SURE YOU ARE
WITH YOUR WIFE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I JUST DIDN'T REALIZE
YOU WERE MARRIED.
OH, WE WERE, BUT
THAT WAS JUST A...
I MEAN, THAT WAS JUST
A BIG DRUNKEN MISTAKE.
YOU'RE BACK.
YOU TWO WERE MARRIED?
OH, WHOOPS, I'M SORRY.
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT EMILY.
CHANDLER, WE SAID
WE WOULD MEET
AT THE COFFEE HOUSE AT 6:00.
WE SAID 7:00.
WE SAID 6:00.
THE ONLY WAY
THAT I SAID 6:00
WOULD BE IF I SAID
THE SENTENCE:
"LET'S MEET AT 7:00,
NOT AT 6:00."
YEAH, AND IF I HAD SAID 7:00
MAYBE I WOULD HAVE SAID
SOMETHING LIKE THIS:
"WOW, MY BOYFRIEND
IS SUCH A WISE ASS, 7:00."
HI.
OH, MY GOOD GOD.
I KNOW WHAT
TIME YOU SAID.
WHAT?
WELL, ACTUALLY, I KNOW WHAT TIME
CHESTER AND MARSHA SAID.
WHAT TIME?
HMM, QUITE AN INTERESTING
TURN OF EVENTS.
SUDDENLY, IT'S MY BOOK
TO THE RESCUE, HUH?
LET'S SEE.
OOH, VERY INTERESTING.
YEAH, WELL, THIS CERTAINLY
CLEARS THINGS UP.
WHAT DOES IT SAY?
I WILL TELL YOU
AS SOON AS YOU THANK ME
FOR WRITING MY BOOK.
THANK YOU
FOR WRITING YOUR BOOK.
IT'S A GREAT BOOK
AND YOU ARE THE QUEEN
OF EVERYTHING.
THANKS, SO ARE YOU.
TOLD YOU I SHOULD NOT WEAR
THIS COLOR.
"MONICA... MARSHA AND CHESTER
"ARE PLANNING ON
SEEING A MOVIE
SUNDAY NIGHT.
"MARSHA THINKS THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO MEET AT 6:00.
CHESTER THINKS IT'S AT 7:00."
SO YOU KNEW
WE WERE GOING TO MISS THE MOVIE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
INSTEAD OF TELLING US
YOU WROTE IT IN
YOUR STUPID BOOK?
"MARSHA AND CHESTER
ARE MAD AT PHYLLIS."
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M GOING TO LOSE THIS JOB.
OH, I'M SO SORRY, MAN.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
YEAH. HELP ME
GET THIS MINI FRIDGE
PAST THE SECURITY GUARD.
( knocking )
HEY, JOEY, I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T
WANT TO TALK TO YOU, WAYNE.
I HATE YOU.
YOU RUINED MY LIFE.
OH. CHANDLER, WAYNE.
WAYNE, CHANDLER.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
JOEY, JOEY, I'LL GET YOU YOUR
JOB BACK IF YOU HELP ME OUT.
WHY SHOULD I HELP YOU OUT?
THE REASON
HE JUST SAID.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
I SAW YOU ON STAGE
TALKING TO THAT
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, SARAH.
I WISH I COULD
TALK TO HER.
WHAT? ARE YOU IN LOVE WITH HER
OR SOMETHING?
YEAH... HER...
ALL OF THEM... ANYONE.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN THERE,
MY FRIEND.
LISTEN, I GUARANTEE
YOU KEEP YOUR JOB
IF YOU CAN TEACH ME HOW
TO TALK TO WOMEN LIKE YOU DO.
OH, WELL, WAYNE...
IT'S NOT REALLY SOMETHING
YOU CAN TEACH, YOU KNOW?
IT'S PRETTY MUCH SOMETHING
YOU'RE BORN WITH...
YOU CAN TEACH IT.
I CAN SHOW YOU HOW TO DO IT.
I MEAN, IF YOU
THINK ABOUT IT
I MEAN, ROSS DID
LEARN SOMETHING
FROM EACH MARRIAGE.
HOW TO MAKE THE NEXT ONE
EVEN SHORTER?
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I MEAN, HE WAS
MARRIED TO ME
A HELL OF A LOT LONGER THAN
HE WAS MARRIED TO EMILY.
HE JUST DIDN'T TELL ME.
MAYBE I HAVE
TO PEE AGAIN.
WELL, THIS IS FUN.
SO, ROSS, DID YOU KILL
ANY OF THESE WIVES?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
YOU KNOW, I CARE A GREAT
DEAL ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER
AND I HAVE TREATED HER
WITH NOTHING BUT RESPECT.
SO, IF YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH ME, FRANKLY, I...
ARE YOU YELLING AT ME?
GOD, NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT, DADDY?
IF YOU DON'T LIKE ROSS,
THAT'S FINE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
I'M GOING TO GO OUT
WITH HIM ANYWAY.
REALLY?
WELL, IF IT DOESN'T
MATTER TO HER
IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
STILL NOT YELLING.
WELL...
WHAT CAN I SAY?
THIS DOESN'T MAKE ME
LIKE YOU ANY BETTER.
THAT'S OKAY,
I'M NOT SO CRAZY ABOUT MYSELF
RIGHT NOW, EITHER.
THEN WE AGREE?
YEAH, YEAH, I GUESS SO.
NEITHER OF US LIKE ROSS.
I LIKE ROSS.
OH... KIDS.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I JUST THOUGHT
OF ANOTHER STORY
ABOUT HOW NICE
ROSS IS.
UH, IT'S OKAY, RACH.
WE'RE NOT LIKING
ROSS RIGHT NOW.
OH, I GOT A LOT
OF THOSE, TOO.
WELL, IT TURNS OUT
YOU WERE RIGHT, C.H.E.E.S.E.
THE SHIPMENT NEVER MADE IT
THROUGH OMAHA?
YOU GOT IT.
AND THE RABBI'S BEARD--
100% HORSEHAIR.
NICE CATCH, C.H.E.E.S.E.
IT'S YOUR LINE, C.H.E.E.S.E.
WAYNE!